Guide to the Sears Family Papers SC0523
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH_2018_001
  - Stanford - Beginning - David and Nancy, 1953-1957 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford - Beginning - David and Nancy, 1953-1957 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Stanford, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Robert R. Sears - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pauline Snedden Sears - Souvenirs, 1966-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pauline Snedden Sears - Souvenirs, 1966-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pauline Snedden Sears - Souvenirs, 1973-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Iowa. Child welfare, League of Women Voters, etc. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Pauline Snedden Sears - Telephone book with some addresses [Stanford] (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pauline Snedden Sears - Address book, circa 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pauline Snedden Sears - Social doings; lists of people to have; menus [Stanford] (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Robert R. Sears. Autobiographical sketch, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Recollections of Robert Sears, 1988 Aug (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Pauline Snedden Sears - Reminiscences of Childhood at Lake Winnipesaukee., 1988 Aug (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hope Snedden Carlsmith - Family genealogy (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ruth Snedden Shoup - Recollections, 1980 Feb (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Harvard. Laboratory of Human Development. Analysis schedule for psychological testing, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Negatives (Box 10)
  - Audio tape (Box 11)